<resources>
	<string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyDPSfWIKGi6Swv00Y-JTKW6-NTSnkeatCQ
	</string>
    <string name="app_name">
        The Purple Pot
    </string>
	<string name="welcomeMsg">
        Welcome to The Purple Pot.
		\n
		\n
		Select \"Find Strains\" below to get started.
    </string>
    <string name="noSavedStrains">
        You dont have any saved strains.\nSearch for strains using the Find Strains page.
    </string>
    <string name="narrowSearch">
        Step 2: Narrow your search.\n(Increase the \'Search Intensity\' to reduce the number of results.)
    </string>
    <string name="findStrainsTip1">
		\n
		\n
        Happiness:\n
		Strains that make you feel happy, uplifted, or relieve depression.\n
		\n
        Euphoria:\n
		Most often described as a tingly (Body High). Produces giggles or feelings of sexual arousal.\n
		\n
        Focus:\n
		Strains that increase focus or creativity.\n
		\n
        Energy:\n
		Similar to Focus but specific to treating fatigue,, providing energy, or makes the user feel talkative or have racing thoughts.\n
		\n
        Relaxation:\n
		Treats stress, anxiety, relaxes muscles, and treats muscle spasms.\n
		\n
        Sleepiness:\n
		Helps treat insomnia, these strains make the user feel sleepy.\n
		\n
        Sickness Relief:\n
		Treats nausea, headaches caused by fever, and inflammation.\n
		\n
        Pain Relief:\n
		Treats pain caused by menstrual or muscle cramps and helps treat migraine headaches.\n
		\n
        Hunger:\n
		Cures lack of appetite, gives the user the munchies.\n
		\n
        Dehydration:\n
		Strains that cause dry mouth, dry eyes, or may imbalance eye pressure.\n
		\n
        Anxiety:\n
		Strains that cause anxiety, stress, paranoia, or dizziness.\n
		\n
		\n
		\n
    </string>

	<string name="findStrainsInfo">
		\n
		Tap on the list to learn about the effects.\n
		\n
		Filters:\n
		\t - omit: Ignores the specified effect. Use this option for effects that you don\'t care if you do or don\'t feel.\n
		\t - min: Minimize or reduce the intensity of the effect.\n
		\t - max: Maximize or increase the presence of the effect.\n
		\n
		\n
		\n
		\n
	</string>

	<string name="supportMessage">
		Please send an email to:
		\n
		\n
		ThePurplePotMobile@gmail.com
		\n
		\n
		for all inquiries.
	</string>
</resources>
